http://www.presbsalado.org/privacy/

Upcoming Events
December 2020 (4)
Monthly Newsletters / History of the Church (The Messenger)
Click for Messengers
Church Library Catalog
Click for Library Catalog
Privacy Statement
The Presbyterian Church of Salado values the privacy of all visitors to http://presbsalado.org. It is the goal of the Presbyterian Church of Salado to honor and respect the privacy of its website visitors and of those who appear on the website in articles, photos, and blog entries.
Squarespace:
Through our webhost, Squarespace Inc. (http://www.squarespace.com), non-identifiable information is logged for analysis purposes. As stated in the Squarespace Privacy Policy (http://www.squarespace.com/privacy/)
“As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.“
Articles, Photos, and Blog Entries:
The Presbyterian Church of Salado Website is a portal for sharing information about our church, its congregation, its mission, and its activities. As such, the website will host photos from church activities, and articles and blog entries about the church and its activities.
Photos taken during Church related functions may be posted without directly receiving permission from the people photographed. However, if anyone should express the desire not to have a photograph shared on the website, the Presbyterian Church of Salado will honor such desires and remove any photos requested. Photographs of minors will not be posted without first receiving permission from the parents/guardians of the minor.
No person’s personal information (phone numbers, email addresses, or mailing addresses) will be shared on the website without previously receiving permission from that person. If anyone should express the desire not to have a particular item of personal information shared on the website, the Presbyterian Church of Salado will honor such desires and remove any items requested.
Presbyterian Church of Salado 105 Salado Plaza Drive, P.O. Box 865 Salado, Texas 76571 (254) 308-2023
Login
